// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q019: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Mr. Shu and Ms. Sanon are colleagues at Arson Group ------ graduated from the same university in Australia.',
      choices: ['which', 'where', 'what', 'who'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['who'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q181',
    },
    {
      question: 'Winston Grocery Store has ------ locations in the city and plans to add two new stores next year.',
      choices: ['multiplying', 'multiple', 'multiply', 'multiplied'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['multiple'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q182',
    },
    {
      question: 'The CEO of Stolzburg Printing Company announced at a press conference yesterday that he ------ next spring.',
      choices: ['retired', 'had retired', 'has retired', 'will retire'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['will retire'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q183',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Srour had to reschedule her dentist appointment because of a scheduling ------ with a business trip to Tokyo.',
      choices: ['conflict', 'garment', 'allowance', 'chance'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['conflict'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q184',
    },
    {
      question: 'Dr. Cho was ------ that his research team would develop a new synthetic fiber by the end of this year.',
      choices: ['capable', 'confident', 'accurate', 'ideal'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['confident'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q185',
    },
    {
      question: 'Please be advised that any changes to meeting room reservations must be made at least one day ------ the date of use.',
      choices: ['so that', 'beforehand', 'prior to', 'whenever'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['prior to'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q186',
    },
    {
      question: 'New measures that will reduce commuting time by car ------.',
      choices: ['are being considered', 'to be considered', 'to conder', 'considering'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['are being considered'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q187',
    },
    {
      question: 'Local residents object ------ to the relocation of the city hospital from the center of the city to the suburbs.',
      choices: ['strength', 'strengthen', 'strongly', 'strong'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['strongly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q188',
    },
    {
      question: 'Discounted subway tickets for travelers were introduced last month and are ------ for three days from the first day of use.',
      choices: ['correct', 'valid', 'favorable', 'original'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['valid'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q189',
    },
    {
      question: 'Please be advised that the Delton Art Museum is not ------ for personal belongings lost in the museum.',
      choices: ['responsibility', 'responsible', 'responsibly', 'response'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['responsible'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題181-190/#q190',
    },
  ],
}